Limited drops trigger a worldwide stampede the instant they go live.
Tickets and limited releases routinely oversell, double-book, and crash — and no one even knows who actually got one.
DROPZERO is a drop platform that never oversells, no matter how many millions hit it at once.
Here's the app — built with v0 and deployed on Vercel.
Stock updates in real time, and a purchase returns a confirmed order.
It speaks eight languages, with full right-to-left layout for Arabic.
Here's the heart of it — one single unit in stock.
We fire two purchases at the very same instant: one to Tokyo, one to Seoul — two different regions.
Amazon Aurora DSQL's multi-region strong consistency means exactly one wins.
Stock never goes negative, and both regions agree on the result.
Now let's scale it: a hundred units, and three thousand concurrent purchases across both regions.
The result — exactly one hundred confirmed, everything else sold out, zero errors.
Thousands of buyers, and we sell precisely our stock — never one more.
Here's how it works. The frontend is on Vercel.
Auth uses OIDC federation to assume an AWS IAM role and mint a DSQL token — zero hardcoded secrets.
Each purchase checks and decrements stock in one transaction; concurrency conflicts are absorbed by retries.
This is only this clean because Aurora DSQL is multi-region and strongly consistent.
Zero oversell is fairness — against bots, against chaos.
Anywhere on earth, everyone sees one single source of truth.
DROPZERO: global drops that never oversell.